quarterlife.com 2009-04-21

# quarterlife

## quarterlife.com privacy policy. 

quarterlife.com.com is a service (the "Service") that allows our members ("Members") to set up personal profiles that can be linked together through a community of friends on our website (the "Website"). The quarterlife.com community allows Members and/or visitors to the Website ("Visitors") to meet new people, share or view user-generated content, and describe their interests. To enhance the utility of the Website and/or the Service, some personal information we ask for is collected and/or displayed to other Members and/or Visitors. In order to fully understand your rights related to privacy issues, quarterlife.com encourages you to review this Privacy Policy. 

####  COLLECTION OF INFORMATION 

quarterlife.com collects Member-submitted personally identifiable information, such as name, e-mail address, and age, to authenticate Members and to send notifications to Members relating to the Website and/or the Service. However, a Memberâ's e-mail address is never shared or displayed to other Members or Visitors. [Will you display birthday or full name on the site?] Members communicate with each other through the Service without disclosing their e-mail addresses. 

quarterlife.com also collects other information for Member profiles. This information is displayed and shared with other Members and/or Visitors to facilitate interaction on the Service. 

quarterlife.com also collects aggregate Member and/or Visitor data and other information that is not personally identifiable for the general management and promotion of the Website and/or the Service, and for tracking usage to continuously improve quarterlife.comâ's offerings. 

In addition, quarterlife.com logs Internet Protocol (IP) addresses from Members and Visitors for security, monitoring, and maintenance purposes. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access pages on the Internet. When you request a page from the Website, our servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address and log this information. 

quarterlife.com may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on the Website. You may be asked to provide personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, e-mail address, phone number, or home address, in order to participate. By entering a quarterlife.com-related promotion, sweepstake or contest, you provide quarterlife.com with express permission to transfer your personal information to a co-sponsor of the promotion/sweepstake/contest, including, but not limited to, an ad partner. Personal information will be used to notify the finalists and/or winners and to award prizes. quarterlife.com and/or a co-sponsor reserve the right to publish names of contest/promotion/sweepstake winners and their cities or towns of residence to ensure transparency in the contest/promotion/sweepstake process and for promotional purposes. In addition, quarterlife.com may transfer personal information to certain ad partners from which you have explicitly requested to receive information. 

####  EDITING OR REMOVING INFORMATION 

Members can edit or remove their profile information and other content at any time by [ ]. In addition, Members have the option of canceling their Membership at any time by [ ] on the Website. 

####  E-MAIL OPT-OUT 

quarterlife.com may use a Member's e-mail address to send updates, notices, newsletters and/or news regarding the Website and/or the Service and/or a Memberâ's friend(s). Members may elect not to receive e-mail of this type by following the instructions contained in the e-mail or by changing their settings on the Website. However, quarterlife.com reserves the right to send e-mail to Members at all times, regardless of their settings, to alert them of material changes to their Membership. 

####  COMMUNICATIONS TO NON-MEMBERS 

Members can invite friends to join the Service by sending invitation e-mails via our automated invitation interface. quarterlife.com stores the e-mail addresses of invitees that a Member provides so that the invitees may be added automatically to that Member's list of friends if they join the Service, and also to send reminders of the invitations. quarterlife.com does not sell these e-mail addresses or use them to send any other communications besides invitations and invitation reminders to join the Service. 

####  COOKIES 

A cookie is a data file that is sent to your browser and is stored on your computerâ's hard drive when you visit a website. quarterlife.com uses cookies to store the preferences of Members and Visitors and to record session information and activity for a variety of purposes, including, but not limited to, helping us understand how Members and Visitors use the Website and/or the Service, and estimating our audience size. This information provides us with the opportunity to improve your quarterlife.com.com experience. quarterlife.com does not use cookies to retrieve any information from your hard drive. quarterlife.com also allows partners, third party advertisers, and ad serving companies, which present content and advertisements on the Website and/or through the Service, to set and access their own cookies on your computer. quarterlife.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed on your computer by third party advertisers or ad serving companies. Use of cookies by third party partners, advertisers and ad serving companies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the quarterlife.com Privacy Policy. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your Internet browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your quarterlife.com.com experience may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. 

####  THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING AND LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES 

quarterlife.com, its partners, or third party advertisers or ad serving companies may deliver ads appearing on the Website and/or through the Service to Members and Visitors. In addition to or in connection with utilizing cookies on your computer, ad servers may compile information about you, including, but not limited to, where you saw their advertisements and which ads you clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to Members and Visitors. The Website and/or the Service may also contain links to websites operated by third parties. It is important to emphasize that quarterlife.com does not control the privacy policies of advertisers and other third party websites for which quarterlife.com provides links and advertisements. If you click through an advertisement or link to a third partyâ's website, you will be subject to that advertiserâ's or third partyâ's privacy policy, which you should review. The quarterlife.com Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Website and/or through the Service. quarterlife.com does not assume responsibility or liability for any third partyâ's policies or actions. 

####  DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION 

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, quarterlife.com will not sell, rent, share, trade, or disclose personal information of its Members and/or Visitors to any third party unless such disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by quarterlife.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to investigate violations of and enforce our Terms of Use Agreement or to otherwise protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of Members or other persons or entities. 

quarterlife.com reserves the right to transfer personal information about Members and/or Visitors to a successor-in-interest or assignee that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale, merger, acquisition, or reorganization of quarterlife.com. 

quarterlife.com also reserves the right to collect, use and supply to third parties aggregated Member and/or Visitor data (independent of any personally identifying information), traffic patterns and analytics regarding the Website and/or the Service for research and commercial purposes, including, but not limited to, describing quarterlife.comâ's Service, Members, and Visitors to partners, prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties. This data is pooled and stripped of personally identifying information and cannot be traced to you specifically. 

####  POSTING INFORMATION 

Whenever a Member posts or discloses personal information on the Website and/or through the Service, that information can be accessed and collected by third parties. In turn, this information can be used by third parties to send Members unsolicited communications or advertisements. quarterlife.com does not control the actions of Members or Visitors. Your disclosure of personal information on the Website and/or through the Service is done so at your own risk. Accordingly, you should be careful and vigilant when disclosing any personal information on the Website and/or through the Service (which is subject to content restrictions described in our Terms of Use Agreement). 

####  SECURITY 

Member accounts are secured by Member-created passwords. quarterlife.com uses reasonable measures to protect the privacy of Member account information that is stored within the quarterlife.com database, and quarterlife.com restricts access to Member information to those employees who need access to such information to perform their job functions, such as quarterlife.comâ's customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that quarterlife.com cannot guarantee the security of Member account information. Unauthorized entry or use of the Website and/or the Service, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of Member information at any time. In addition, transmissions over the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. It may be possible for third parties to intercept and access private information you transmit through the Service. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. quarterlife.com does not assume any liability for disclosure of personal information or other data, including, without limitation, any disclosure resulting from errors in transmission, unauthorized entry or use of the Website and/or the Service, or hardware or software failure. 

####  CHILDRENâ'S POLICY 

quarterlife.com.com is intended solely for use by persons 14 years of age or older. All persons under 14 years of age are prohibited from registering on the Service or using the Website. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personally identifying information from a child under the age of 14, such as full name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child, we will promptly delete that data from our systems. 

####  AMENDMENTS TO THE QUARTERLIFE.COM PRIVACY POLICY 

quarterlife.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. quarterlife.com will post on the Website any amendments to this Privacy Policy so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Such amendments will be effective immediately upon the posting thereof. Your continued use of the Website and/or the Service following posting of such amendments will constitute your acceptance of those changes, provided, however, that if quarterlife.com plans to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, quarterlife.com will notify you via e-mail or by placing a prominent notice on the Website for 30 days. 

####  ACCEPTANCE OF THE QUARTERLIFE.COM PRIVACY POLICY 

By registering as a Member of the Service and/or using the Website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy, you should no longer use the Website and/or the Service. 

####  QUESTIONS REGARDING THE QUARTERLIFE.COM PRIVACY POLICY 

Any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of quarterlife.com, or your dealings with quarterlife.com may be addressed by e-mailing us at [ ].
